Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6 Locals, 2.
  - Local 624 (Fairmount, WV)
    - Local 624 (Fairmount, WV) Correspondence, April 22, 1941 - June 8, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Harley to Julius Emspak Regarding Charter, May 7, 1941; 2. (Box 10, Folder 60, Item 2)
      - Neil Brant Telegram to Matles Regarding Certification, June 2, 1942; 3. (Box 10, Folder 60, Item 3)
      - Charles Newell to Matles Regarding Sunbury Westinghouse with News Clipping, June 8, 1942; 4. (Box 10, Folder 60, Item 4)
  - Local 624 (Muncy, PA)
    - Local 624 (Muncy, PA) General Incoming Correspondence, June 12, 1945 - March 6, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Julius Emspak to Charles Burk Regarding Supplies, June 12, 1945; 1. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Burk Regarding Finances, July 19, 1945; 2. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Ray McCowan Regarding Military Personnel, September 26, 1945; 3. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Burk Regarding UE News, September 28, 1945; 4. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Lloyd Lute Regarding Robinson Manufacturing Strike, June 6, 1946; 5. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 5)
      - Emspak to McCowan Regarding Finances, December 11, 1946; 6. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Clara Feiring Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits with Emspak Letter to Burk, March 6, 1950; 7. (Box 10, Folder 61, Item 7)
    - Local 624 (Muncy, PA) General Outgoing Correspondence, August 17, 1945 - June 20, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - William Likens to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 20, 1946; 1. (Box 10, Folder 62, Item 1)
      - Ray McCowan to UE Regarding Military Personnel with Ray Memo to Thelma, August 17, 1945; 2. (Box 10, Folder 62, Item 2)
    - Local 624 (Muncy, PA) Finances, April - September 21, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Supply Requisition, September 21, 1945; 1. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 1)
      - Stamps, May 22, 1945; 2. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 2)
      - Lerman Brothers, Shipping Memo, May 28, 1945; 3. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 3)
      - Servicemen UE News Statement, April 1945; 4. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 4)
      - Servicemen UE News Statement, May 1945; 5. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 5)
      - Charter Supply List, May 15, 1945; 6. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 6)
      - Servicemen UE News Statement, June 1945; 7. (Box 10, Folder 63, Item 7)
    - Local 624 (Muncy, PA) United Steelworkers Inter-Union Rivalry, February 22 - March 10, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Al Ellis to James Matles, February 22, 1954; 1. (Box 10, Folder 64, Item 1)
      - Ellis Telegram to UE, March 10, 1954; 2. (Box 10, Folder 64, Item 2)
    - Local 624 (Muncy, PA) Correspondence, March 6, 1946 - March 6, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Robinson Manufacturing, Notification of Pending Disagreement, March 6, 1946; 1. (Box 10, Folder 65, Item 1)
      - Stanley Loney Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits, March 6, 1950; 2. (Box 10, Folder 65, Item 2)
      - Report of Lloy Lutz Regarding Local 624 Robinson Manufacturing Collective Bargaining, 3. (Box 10, Folder 65, Item 3)
  - Local 624 (Swissvale, PA)
    - Local 624 (Swissvale, PA) Correspondence, 1964 - 1976 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Local 624 (Swissvale, PA) Correspondence, 1976 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Local 625
    - Local 625 Officers Lists, March 20, 1943 - August 21, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Local 625 General Incoming Correspondence, November 9, 1943 - September 26, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Julius Emspak to Clifford Croushore Regarding Finances, November 9, 1943; 1. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Roy Fetter Regarding Finances, November 22, 1943; 2. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Croushore Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 10, 1945; 3. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Walter Smith Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits, January 24, 1950; 4. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Croushore Regarding Finances, February 8, 1954; 5. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 5)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Charles Giron, August 20, 1946; 6. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 6)
      - James Matles to Smith Regarding Staff Members, February 25, 1952; 7. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 7)
      - Russ Nixon to Hilton Kirk Regarding Political Action Committee, November 3, 1947; 8. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 8)
      - Basil Pollitt to John Melville Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits, September 26, 1955; 9. (Box 10, Folder 69, Item 9)
    - Local 625 General Outgoing Correspondence, November 25, 1941 - March 6, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Clifford Croushore to UE Regarding Address, June 1943; 1. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 1)
      - Croushore to General Executive Board Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 6, 1945; 2. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 2)
      - Roy Fetter to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, November 1943; 3. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 3)
      - Charles Griffin to Zappone Engineering Company Regarding Local 625 Collective Bargaining, undated; 4. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 4)
      - Hilton Kirk to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 9, 1947; 5. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 5)
      - Kirk to Russ Nixon Regarding PAC, January 23, 1948; 6. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 6)
      - Walter Smith to Emspak Regarding Local 625 Constitution and Officers, September 26, 1949; 7. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 7)
      - Smith to UE Regarding General Cable Strike, October 3, 1952; 8. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 8)
      - Clyde Thomas to Lyle Dowling Regarding Foreign Policy and Congress of Industrial Organizations with November 20, 1941, William Vandervort Telegram to Phillip Murray, November 25, 1941; 9. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 9)
      - Thomas to Emspak Regarding Local 625 Constitution, January 12, 1942; 10. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 10)
      - William Whigham to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding UN Employment with March 14, 1955, Fitzgerald Letters to Whigham and Daniel Marguriet, March 6, 1955; 11. (Box 10, Folder 70, Item 11)
    - Local 625 Greensburg, PA, Correspondence, 1957 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Local 625 Railway and Industrial Engineering Clippings and Correspondence, 1976 - 1983 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Local 625 Salary and Expense Letters, Lloyd Makin, January 9 - October 28, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Local 625 Bond Form and Questionnaire, October 1941 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Local 625 Chartering, August 19 - 26, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - William Chambers to Julius Emspak, August 19, 1941; 1. (Box 10, Folder 75, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Chambers, August 26, 1941; 2. (Box 10, Folder 75, Item 2)
      - Charter Application, August 1941; 3. (Box 10, Folder 75, Item 3)
    - Local 625 Audit, June 20 - August 20, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - William Klingensmit to Hilton Kirk, June 20, 1946; 1. (Box 10, Folder 76, Item 1)
      - Klingensmit to General Executive Board, August 15, 1946; 2. (Box 10, Folder 76, Item 2)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Thomas Fitzpatrick, August 20, 1946; 3. (Box 10, Folder 76, Item 3)
      - Fitzgerald to Klingensmit, August 20, 1946; 4. (Box 10, Folder 76, Item 4)
    - Local 625 Correspondence and Reports, December 16, 1941 - April 19, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - William Chambers to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 625 Officers, December 16, 1941; 1. (Box 10, Folder 77, Item 1)
      - Audit Report, June 1943; 2. (Box 10, Folder 77, Item 2)
      - Status of Our Negotiations, June 18, 1952; 3. (Box 10, Folder 77, Item 3)
      - Paul Clark to James Matles Regarding Finances, February 2, 1954; 4. (Box 10, Folder 77, Item 4)
      - Richard Niebur to Nathan Spero Regarding Local 625 Railway and Industrial Engineering Strike, April 19, 1954; 5. (Box 10, Folder 77, Item 5)
    - Local 625 Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1967 - 1973 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Local 625 Strikes, Subsidies, and Other Monies, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Local 626 (Pittsburgh)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) General Incoming Correspondence, December 26, 1941 - June 15, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Marino Regarding Supplies, November 26, 1941; 1. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Marino Regarding Supplies, December 29, 1941; 2. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Marino Regarding Supplies, January 6, 1942; 3. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Marino Regarding Supplies, January 13, 1942; 4. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Marino Regarding Supplies, January 22, 1942; 5. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Victor Brandon Regarding Supplies, May 26, 1942; 6. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Brandon Regarding Supplies, July 1, 1942; 7. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Brandon Regarding Supplies, July 22, 1942; 8. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Brandon Regarding Supplies, July 28, 1942; 9. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Ice Members of Local 626 Regarding Factionalism and Charter Revocation, June 15, 1943; 10. (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) General Outgoing Correspondence, October 10, 1941 - May 28, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Thomas Brady to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 28, 1943; 1. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Brady to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 13, 1943; 2. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Victor Brandon to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 30, 1942; 3. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Brandon to Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 6, 1942; 4. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Brandon to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 2, 1942; 5. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Brandon to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 4, 1942; 6. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Brandon Telegram to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, June 30, 1942; 7. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Brandon to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment with Stamp Balance Sheet, July 19, 1942; 8. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Brandon to Emspak Regarding Unemployment Finances, August 12, 1942; 9. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Brandon to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, September 21, 1942; 10. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - August Gliniecki to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 11, 1942; 11. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Frank Kocka to Emspak Regarding Local 626 Organization and Finances, October 10, 1941; 12. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Kocka to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 8, 1941; 13. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Kocka to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 10, 1941; 14. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Joseph Marino Telegram to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 1942; 15. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Marino to UE Regarding Supplies, December 1941; 16. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 16)
      - Ralph Welker Telegram to Emspak Regarding Suspension, March 20, 1942; 17. (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Railway and Engineering Industrial Correspondence, 1976 - 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Receipts, October 28, 1941 - December 15, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Per Capita Reports, November 1941 - April 1943 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Supply Requisitions, October 23, 1941 - June 18, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Stamps, October 30, 1941 - November 20, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Requisitions, February 23 - July 22, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Notice of Delinquency or Suspension, November 1941 - October 1942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Finances, September 2, 1941 - March 26, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Charter Supply List, September 2, 1941; 1. (Box 11, Folder 10, Item 1)
      - Bond Questionnaire, November 19, 1941; 2. (Box 11, Folder 10, Item 2)
      - Bond Form, June 8, 1942; 3. (Box 11, Folder 10, Item 3)
      - Bond Questionnaire, June 1942; 4. (Box 11, Folder 10, Item 4)
      - Steward Thomas Brady Dues Payment List, March 26, 1943; 5. (Box 11, Folder 10, Item 5)
      - Savings Account Pass Book, March 1943; 6. (Box 11, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Organization, September 26 - December 16, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Julius Emspak to William Chambers, September 26, 1941; 1. (Box 11, Folder 11, Item 1)
      - Chambers to Emspak Regarding, September 29, 1941; 2. (Box 11, Folder 11, Item 2)
      - Robert Davis to Nat Geller, December 3, 1941; 3. (Box 11, Folder 11, Item 3)
      - Geller Telegram to Davis, December 5, 1946; 4. (Box 11, Folder 11, Item 4)
      - Davis Telegram to Emspak, December 16, 1941; 5. (Box 11, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) War Conversion, June 11 - July 8, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Russ Nixon to Victor Brandon, June 11, 1942; 1. (Box 11, Folder 12, Item 1)
      - Nixon to Brandon, July 8, 1942; 2. (Box 11, Folder 12, Item 2)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Secession, May 10, 1943 - June 5, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Fred Haug to David Scribner with May 8, 1943, Hugh Sperry and Paul Shupp Letters to Haug, May 10, 1943; 1. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 1)
      - Stipulation for Appointment of Hearing Officer, June 24, 1943; 2. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 2)
      - Haug Memo to James Matles with June 24, 1943, Leaflet, "Standard Sanitary Workers", June 26, 1943; 3. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 3)
      - Scribner Memo, June 26, 1943; 4. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 4)
      - Haug to Matles with Leaflet, "The Committee of Eight", July 28, 1943; 5. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 5)
      - Leo Turner to Scribner, May 26, 1944; 6. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 6)
      - Sylvan Libson to Turner, June 5, 1944; 7. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 7)
      - Suspension of Local 626, June 1943; 8. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 8)
      - Allan Haywood to Albert Fitzgerald, July 13, 1943; 9. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 9)
      - Fitzgerald to Haywood, July 15, 1943; 10. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 10)
      - Haywood to Fitzgerald with June 29, 1943, Harry Alan Sherman Letter to Phillip Murray, July 20, 1943; 11. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 11)
      - Haywood Telegram to Fitzgerald, August 30, 1943; 12. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 12)
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Haywood, August 30, 1943; 13. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 13)
      - Memo, 1943; 14. (Box 11, Folder 13, Item 14)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Correspondence, February 2 - March 17, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Robert Davis to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 2, 1942; 1. (Box 11, Folder 14, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Fred Haug Regarding Finances, March 17, 1942; 2. (Box 11, Folder 14, Item 2)
    - Local 626 (Pittsburgh) Newspaper Clipping, July 1943 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Local 626 (Greensburg)
    - Local 626 (Greensburg) General Incoming Correspondence, February 11, 1946 - November 25, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Julius Emspak to Arem Foti Regarding Veterans and Finances, February 11, 1946; 1. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Ralph Kromer Regarding Supplies, February 27, 1946; 2. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Foti Regarding Finances, December 10, 1946; 3. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Betty Yanuck Regarding Tafty-Hartley Affidavits, January 24, 1959; 4. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Kromer Regarding UE Constitution, February 26, 1951; 5. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Charles Stewart Regarding Finances, February 5, 1952; 6. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 6)
      - Emspak to John Sofranko Regarding International Harvester, Marathon and General Cable Strikes, February 25, 1953; 7. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Louis Rosmus Regarding Finances, November 25, 1955; 8. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 8)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Stewart Regarding District 6, November 12, 1952; 9. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 9)
      - Thomas Fitzpatrick to Kromer Regarding Political Action Committee, September 29, 1947; 10. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 10)
      - James Matles to Susan Chrisman Regarding Staff Members, February 25, 1952; 11. (Box 11, Folder 16, Item 11)
    - Local 626 (Greensburg) General Outgoing Correspondence, February 6 - November 27, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Arem Foti to Julius Emspak Regarding Veterans Finances, February 6, 1946; 1. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 1)
      - Foti to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 27, 1946; 2. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 2)
      - Ray Griffin Telegram to James Matles Regarding Local 626 I. T. E. Circuit Breaker Strike, November 14, 1951; 3. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 3)
      - Ralph Kromer to Emspak Regarding Finances, Supplies and Membership, February 18, 1946; 4. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 4)
      - Kromer to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 626 Constitution, February 5, 1951; 5. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 5)
      - Louis Rosmus to UE Regarding Finances, November 21, 1955; 6. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 6)
      - John Sofranko to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 19, 1953; 7. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 7)
      - Charles Stewart to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 22, 1956; 8. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 8)
      - Stewart to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 4, 1956; 9. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 9)
      - Stewart to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and District 6, November 3, 1952; 10. (Box 11, Folder 17, Item 10)
    - Local 626 (Greensburg) Correspondence, 1956 - 1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Local 626 (Greensburg) Correspondence, 1968 - 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Local 626 (Greensburg) Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1975 - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Local 626 Organization, January 3 - February 27, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak, January 3, 1946; 1. (Box 11, Folder 21, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Turner, January 9, 1946; 2. (Box 11, Folder 21, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Thomas Fitzpatrick, January 9, 1946; 3. (Box 11, Folder 21, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Turner, February 27, 1946; 4. (Box 11, Folder 21, Item 4)
    - Local 626 Correspondence, Secretary to Emspak to Stanley Loney, February 26, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Local 626 Newspaper Clipping, November 14, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Local 627
    - Local 627 Officers Lists, December 1943 - December 10, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Local 627 Executive Board Resolution Regarding Factionalism, February 11, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Local 627 Fred Phillips Incoming Correspondence, February 6, 1946 - June 7, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - William Cahn Regarding Publicity, February 6, 1946; 1. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 1)
      - Cahn Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 27, 1946; 2. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 2)
      - William Click Regarding Dues Check-Off, August 30, 1946; 3. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 3)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 12, 1946; 4. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 4)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, August 14, 1947; 5. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 5)
      - Emspak Regarding Dues Check-Off, June 7, 1948; 6. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 6)
      - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, February 24, 1948; 7. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 7)
      - Clifford McAvoy Regarding Political Action Committee, October 7, 1946; 8. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 8)
      - David Scribner Regarding Overtime, September 24, 1946; 9. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 9)
      - Scribner Regarding Local 627 Constitution and Factionalism, March 14, 1947; 10. (Box 11, Folder 26, Item 10)
    - Local 627 Fred Phillips Outgoing Correspondence, January 29, 1946 - June 2, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Phillips to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 627 Westinghouse Strike, January 29, 1946; 1. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 1)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Local 627 Westinghouse Strike, February 1, 1946; 2. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 2)
      - Phillips Telegram to David Scribner Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 25, 1946; 3. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 3)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-Off, August 23, 1946; 4. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 4)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-Off, August 31, 1946; 5. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 5)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 2, 1946; 6. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 6)
      - Phillips to Clifford McAvoy Regarding Political Action and Political Action Committee, October 2, 1946; 7. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 7)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 9, 1946; 8. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 8)
      - Phillips to David Scribner Regarding Finances, February 6, 1947; 9. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 9)
      - Phillips to Scribner Regarding Local 627 Constitution and Factionalism, March 11, 1947; 10. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 10)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, July 29, 1947; 11. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 11)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, August 30, 1947; 12. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 12)
      - Phillips Telegram to Russ Nixon Regarding PAC, October 11, 1947; 13. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 13)
      - Phillips to R. E. Regarding PAC, October 16, 1947; 14. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 14)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 8, 1947; 15. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 15)
      - Phillips to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting and Political Action, February 14, 1948; 16. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 16)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding PAC, March 13, 1948; 17. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 17)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Publicity, May 11, 1948; 18. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 18)
      - Phillips Telegram to Emspak Regarding Publicity, May 11, 1948; 19. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 19)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-Off, May 18, 1948; 20. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 20)
      - Phillips to Emspak Regarding Publicity, June 2, 1948; 21. (Box 11, Folder 27, Item 21)
    - Local 627 General Incoming Correspondence, January 5, 1942 - February 13, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - William Cahn to William Parker Regarding Publicity, March 11, 1946; 1. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 1)
      - Julius Emspak to Dorothy Burnworth Regarding Finances, January 5, 1942; 2. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Burnworth Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 624 and 627, July 7, 1943; 3. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Helene Clowser Regarding Veterans and Finances, June 27, 1945; 4. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 4)
      - Emspak to William Parker Regarding Local 627 Westinghouse Strike, March 23, 1946; 5. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Madelon Phillips Regarding Local 627 Westinghouse Strike, April 5, 1946; 6. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Frances Huey Regarding Political Action Committee, October 28, 1947; 7. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Huey Regarding PAC, November 6, 1947; 8. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 8)
      - Emspak to John Everhart Regarding Factionalism, February 17, 1948; 9. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Huey Regarding PAC, February 18, 1948; 10. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 10)
      - Emspak to William Wither Regarding Finances, January 9, 1951; 11. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 11)
      - Emspak to Withers Regarding Finances, June 7, 1951; 12. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 12)
      - Emspak to Withers Regarding Finances, June 29, 1951; 13. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Withers Regarding Finances, February 13, 1953; 14. (Box 11, Folder 28, Item 14)
    - Local 627 General Incoming Correspondence, 1942 - May 15, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - David Scribner Telegram to Dorothy Webb Regarding Political Action, 1942; 1. (Box 11, Folder 29, Item 1)
      - A. N. Towsen to Betty Morris Regarding Childcare, April 18, 1944; 2. (Box 11, Folder 29, Item 2)
      - Towsen to Morris Regarding Childcare, April 19, 1944; 3. (Box 11, Folder 29, Item 3)